Ningninghou: So it's like this.
Ningninghou: Let's scout the area first.
Ningninghou: Nan, you cover this area, ok?
Nan Nandu: Okay.
Ningninghou: This area.
Jin Jinliang: Then I'll cover that area.
Ningninghou: You cover that area.
Ke Ke'ai: I'll check the dining table.
He Heda: Then I'll take this area.
Ningninghou: This area.
Nan Nandu: There's one up here too.
Nan Nandu: Take a look and memorize it.
He Heda: Okay.
Countdown begins.
Ningninghou: Check that one too.
Dingdingdang: One under this table.
Li Liwo: I hear a sound.
Li Liwo: There's an Assassin!
Li Liwo: Someone's here!
Li Liwo: There's someone here!
He Heda: Hold on.
Li Liwo: What?
Li Liwo: Who's there?
Li Liwo: Over there!
Li Liwo: What was that sound?
30 seconds deducted.
Li Liwo: What... what is this?
Li Liwo: What is this thing?
Li Liwo: It's not human!
Li Liwo: What else?
Ningninghou: What else is there?
Li Liwo: Who... who is this?
30 seconds deducted.
Ah!
Oh my god!
Li Liwo: It's over!
Li Liwo: This room is full of people!
Li Liwo: Now it's over!
Ah!
Li Liwo: That's so scary!
Dingdingdang: No, let's be bold for once.
Dingdingdang: We'll lose this anyway.
Dingdingdang: Quick!
Dingdingdang: Be bold, look quickly!
Li Liwo: That's not right.
Jin Jinliang: Is there a key?
30 seconds deducted.
Countdown ends.
Challenge failed.
Please stay where you are.
Wait 3 minutes for countdown to restart.
He Heda: Let's rest for a minute.
Ningninghou: You guys just now...
Ningninghou: Why did you come over here?
Ningninghou: Are you done searching there?
Nan Nandu: I checked everything there.
Ningninghou: Checked every box and drawer?
Nan Nandu: Yes, checked them all.
Ningninghou: Nothing on the dining table?
Nan Nandu: Nothing there either.
Ningninghou: No need to go there, right?
He Heda: Then get ready and let's start.
Dingdingdang: Start.
Jin Jinliang: Okay, let's go.
Ke Ke'ai: You didn't search there, right?
Jin Jinliang: Let's start.
He Heda: Didn't search.
Ke Ke'ai: I'll check there. He Heda: Okay.
Jin Jinliang: Start the timer.
Countdown begins.
Ah!
Li Liwo: There's an Assassin!
Li Liwo: What the heck is making noise?